(801) 427-7833 kredfox4@gmail.com

https://github.com/107124 https://www.linkedin.com/in/kenttaylor-129282168/

Summary

Ever since I was a little kid, I've always had a passion for technology and creating things. Now, from front end design to background development, I create clean, powerful, yet simple designs and functions that are easy to use. I focus on the user experience as they click through the compositions on their screen. Employers and managers come to me for my passion for technology and problem solving, and to gather sufficient ideas for improvement and because I straight up get things done.

Skills

- Javascript, ReactJS, Python 3, C#, C++, HTML5, CSS, Flask, JSON, Git, MongoDB, SQL Databases, SCSS/SASS, Flexbox, CSS Grid.
- Design Tools: Visual Studio Code, Postman, Heroku, GitHub.
- Certificate in Technical Support Fundamentals (IT)
 - License: AF2RGVC9T3D2
 - Includes: Computer Hardware, Computer Software, Networking, Security, Documentation, Problem Solving and Basic IT Literacy.

Projects

Portfolio Project: A portfolio application integrating and using API's, built with React JS, JSX, CSS, SCSS, and Node.js. Site layout with CSS Grid and Flexbox. Includes user authentication and CRUD functionality via API's and AXIOS.

Fantastic Fries: A multi page, responsive restaurant website that utilizes HTML5, CSS3, Flexbox, CSS Grid, Animations, media queries, custom forms, responsive images, and a range of front end development techniques.

https://determined-sinoussi-b6e667.netlify.com/

Work Experience

RX VERIFICATION SPECIALIST - DEC, 2015 - MAY, 2019

Verifying customer/patients prescriptions to make sure that they match their orders for their contact lenses. Customer service, speed and accuracy with great communications skills are the priority. Problem solving and a good eye for details in a fast paced environment are required in this current job.

Through the creation of a program that I had built by myself for 1800contacts, I was able to cut the time that an employee writes an email or text to a customer from an average of 3 minutes to an average of 17 seconds. This saved time and money and an increase in customer service/satisfaction.

PORT OF SUBS ASSISTANT MANAGER – 2010-2012 AND 2014-2015

I was hired to help open and grow a new franchise to the state of Utah. Provided onsite training for new employees and their progression to prepare them for new locations throughout the state. I was the closing manager which consisted of on the cent accuracy of daily total sales and reports, as well as inventory. I altered the way we train to help employees be more effective and better with their customer service and experience. I found new ways to bring in more customers during slow hours to increase sales by coming up with our "Happy Hour" promotion and designed the advertisements along with marketing. Doing so increased customer traffic by 24%.

Education

Utah Valley University: August 2014 - January 2019

- 2 years of Software Engineering
- 2 years of Music Education

Google IT Certification: January 2019

Bottega: May 2019 - August 2019

References

Jay Taylor (Port of Subs Franchise Owner): (775) 772-9096

Jason Andersen (1800contacts Co-Head of Compliance): (385) 224-2132

Chelsea Laws (1800contacts Compliance Manager): (801) 867-1653